<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Hiptoro]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Buzzworthy Entertainment, Anime, Sports, and Pop Culture]]></description>
        <link>www.hiptoro.com</link>
        <image>
            <url>www.hiptoro.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/unnamed.png</url>
            <title>Hiptoro</title>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com</link>
        </image>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 07:49:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="www.hiptoro.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 07:48:56 GMT</pubDate>
        <copyright><![CDATA[All rights reserved 2023, Ibas]]></copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jujutsu Kaisen Season 2 Major Spoilers Leaked Ahead of Release]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Before its release, Jujutsu Kaisen Season 2 brought a new set of character designs. Various new characters have been redesigned for season 2 of the popular anime series, which will deliver a completely different viewing experience. The first trailer of the Jujutsu Kaisen Season 2 has given a glimpse of the show&#8217;s new character design [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/jujutsu-kaisen-season-2-spoilers-release</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/jujutsu-kaisen-season-2-spoilers-release</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Alien Film First Look: Iconic Facehugger Returns in Standalone Movie]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Behind-the-Scenes Glimpse We&#8217;ve finally got an update on the upcoming Alien film, which was shared on the official Alien Twitter account earlier today. In a post for Alien Day — an online event from 20th Century Films sharing reveals and news about the franchise — we got a behind-the-scenes glimpse of the new Alien film [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/alien-first-look-at-new-movie-the-return-of</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/alien-first-look-at-new-movie-the-return-of</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Boruto Chapter 81 Spoilers: Boruto Likely to Associate with Unlikely Character Against Kawaki]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Will Code and Boruto team up to fight Kawaki? Possible spoilers for Boruto chapter 81 might have the possible answer to this question. Read on to find out more. Will Code and Boruto team up in Boruto chapter 81? Kawaki put away Boruto&#8217;s parents in the Daikokuten dimension and they probably won&#8217;t be seen anytime [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/boruto-chapter-81-spoilers-code</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/boruto-chapter-81-spoilers-code</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Latest Chainsaw Man Chapter 129 Spoilers, Release Date, Read Online, Raw Scans and More]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The upcoming release of Chainsaw Man Chapter 129 has generated high expectations among fans after the startling revelation in the last chapter. The recent Chainsaw Man chapter has breathed new life into the story. Not only did it progress the fight between Asa, Denji, and the Falling Devil, but it also introduced a fresh character [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/chainsaw-man-chapter-129-spoilers-release-date</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/chainsaw-man-chapter-129-spoilers-release-date</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jujutsu Kaisen Chapter 222 Spoilers, Read Online, Release Date, Chapter 221 Review, Raw Scan, and More]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The release date for Jujutsu Kaisen Chapter 222 has been announced, and we have all the needed information in this article. Spoilers ahead! Jujutsu Kaisen is an action-adventure Manga written by Gege Akutami. The manga follows Itadori Yuji. Yuji gets possessed by Sukuna, who uses Yuji&#8217;s body as a vessel. The story then progresses after [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/jujutsu-kaisen-chapter-222-spoilers-read-online</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/jujutsu-kaisen-chapter-222-spoilers-read-online</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Horrifying UFO Story from Brazil's Roswell: Joe Rogan's Guest James Fox Shares Chilling Varginha Incident Details]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction James Fox, the creator of the famous UFO documentary &#8220;Moment of Contact,&#8221; shared a terrifying UFO story with Joe Rogan that would leave anyone sleepless at night. The story covers the Varginha UFO incident in Brazil in 1996, sometimes called “The Roswell of Brazil” or “Brazil’s Roswell.” The Varginha UFO Incident The 1996 incident [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/joe-rogan-guest-shares-horrifying-ufo-story</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/joe-rogan-guest-shares-horrifying-ufo-story</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sigourney Weaver Confirms No Return as Ellen Ripley in Upcoming "Alien" Movie: Blomkamp Sequel and New Film Details]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The End of Ripley? Sigourney Weaver has confirmed that she will not be reprising her role as Ellen Ripley in the &#8220;Alien&#8221; franchise. In a recent interview with Total Film magazine, Weaver stated that &#8220;there are all kinds of younger actors taking this kind of role.&#8221; She also revealed that the ship had sailed on [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/sigourney-weaver-wont-reprise-her-role-in-alien</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/sigourney-weaver-wont-reprise-her-role-in-alien</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[My Hero Academia Chapter 387 Spoilers, Predictions: Fight Between All Might and All For One]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[My Hero Academia chapter 387 spoilers are being awaited by fans all over the globe after All Might made a comeback in the previous chapter. My Hero Academia chapter 387 spoilers and predictions All Might come back to fight his lifetime opponent All For One, in the previous chapter. This got a lot of the fans [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/my-hero-academia-chapter-387-spoilers-prediction</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/my-hero-academia-chapter-387-spoilers-prediction</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One Punch Man Season 3 Release Date, Plot and New Episodes Delay Reason After Season 2 Ending]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[One Punch Man Season 3 is set to release soon. OPM has been a hit among the fans, and now fans can&#8217;t wait for the next installment in the anime. One Punch Man is illustrated by ONE. It was first posted by ONE on his blogs, but soon after it got popular, Shueisha&#8217;s Young Jump [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/one-punch-man-season-3-release-date-plot</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/one-punch-man-season-3-release-date-plot</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Gun Kelly's Wild 33rd Birthday: Flamethrowers, Marijuana, and Police Visits, but No Megan Fox Appearance]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Party: Flamethrowers, Marijuana, and Police Visits Machine Gun Kelly, the famous rapper, and rocker, recently celebrated his 33rd birthday in style. The party, held at his Los Angeles home, was a wild affair that featured flamethrowers, marijuana, and even a visit from the police. In several posts on his Instagram account, MGK shared photos [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/machine-gun-kellys-33rd-birthday-no-megan-fox</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/machine-gun-kellys-33rd-birthday-no-megan-fox</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kingdom Chapter 756 LEAKED! Read Online, Spoilers, Raw Scans, Release Date, Review and More]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Kingdom Chapter 756 spoilers and raw scans are released, and fans have a lot to look forward to. Here&#8217;s a quick review of everything that has been leaked so far and how you can read them online. Kingdom is a historical manga series, a masterpiece created and illustrated by Yasuhisa Hara. Since January 2006, it [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/kingdom-chapter-756-leaked-read-online-spoilers-raw-scans-release-date-review-and-more</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/kingdom-chapter-756-leaked-read-online-spoilers-raw-scans-release-date-review-and-more</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Netflix One Piece Live Action Movie Release date, Spoilers, Plot, Cast and More]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[One Piece live action movie adaptation is to premiere on Netflix in 2023, as confirmed by a recent announcement and Matt Owens&#8217; statement. As the premiere of One Piece live action approaches, fans are combing through the internet for any additional release details. Regrettably, no reliable information beyond the series&#8217; expected year of release is [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/netflix-one-piece-live-action-release-date-spoil</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/netflix-one-piece-live-action-release-date-spoil</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Christian Bale admitted that he was envious of Ben Affleck when he was first cast as Batman.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In Christopher Nolan&#8217;s Dark Knight trilogy, Christian Bale headed one of the most successful Batman series to date. The actor worked on the character for seven years and helped Batman become the first billion-dollar superhero film at the time. Although Christian Bale was happy with retiring the character at the end of his stint, things [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/christian-bale-envious-ben-affleck</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/christian-bale-envious-ben-affleck</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Will there be an AMC Lucky Hank Season 2? Release Date, Cast, Renewal Status and Everything Else You Need to Know]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Will AMC greenlight Lucky Hank Season 2? Bob Odenkirk has had a successful partnership with AMC, having been a crucial part of the network&#8217;s success with the Breaking Bad franchise over the last decade. Better Call Saul has been wildly popular since its inception. With the announcement of a new AMC drama, Lucky Hank, fans [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/lucky-hank-season-2-bob-odenkirk-breaking-bad</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/lucky-hank-season-2-bob-odenkirk-breaking-bad</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ben Affleck claims that he fell in love with Jennifer Lopez because she was 'the kind of girl I went to high school with']]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Ben Affleck and Jennifer Lopez were the most visible Hollywood couple from 2002 to 2004. They were dubbed &#8220;Bennifer&#8221; by reporters, and they were even engaged. The publicity wasn&#8217;t always flattering, and it only got worse once they split up. With 17 years between them, Affleck can look back fondly on happier days. On January [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/ben-affleck-fell-in-love-with-jennifer-lopez</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/ben-affleck-fell-in-love-with-jennifer-lopez</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ben Affleck faced a 'massive sense of embarrassment' following an Oscars chat with Dustin Hoffman]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Timothy Affleck, Ben Affleck&#8217;s father, has frequently come up in interviews throughout the years. In a December 2021 interview, Ben Affleck recounted a specific incident at the Academy Awards that transformed his perception of his father. It&#8217;s not because of Timothy&#8217;s words but because of Oscar winner Dustin Hoffman. Ben Affleck grew up thinking his [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/ben-affleck-oscar-chat-dustin-hoffman</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/ben-affleck-oscar-chat-dustin-hoffman</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Mandalorian Season 4 Release Date Update, Renewal Status 2023: Will The Series Get Cancelled Amid Dwindling Ratings for Season 3 and New Star Wars Shows?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The space-western series The Mandalorian, set in the Star Wars universe, concluded its third season on April 19, 2023, leaving viewers eagerly anticipating The Mandalorian Season 4. Starring Pedro Pascal as Din Djarin, the Disney+ original series premiered on November 12 and now fans can expect the fourth season to bring more excitement and adventure [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/the-mandalorian-season-4-release-date-update</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/the-mandalorian-season-4-release-date-update</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One Piece Chapter 1082 Release Date, Spoilers: Are The Blackbeard Pirates Incoming?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[One Piece Chapter 1082 is set to publish soon as the illustrator and author Echiiro Oda is back from his break. The previous chapter&#8217;s events, in which Law and the Heart Pirates were beaten by Teach, raised anticipation among the fans. The remaining characters are now in a challenging crisis, leaving fans to wonder what [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/one-piece-chapter-1082-release-date-spoilers-oda</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/one-piece-chapter-1082-release-date-spoilers-oda</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Courteney Cox divulges details of a paranormal encounter she had at her 'haunted' home: At first, I didn't believe]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[According to Courteney Cox, she sold her house after learning it was haunted. The 57-year-old actress was promoting her upcoming horror comedy series Shining Vale when she spoke on Jimmy Kimmel Live about the troublesome ghost who resided in her former townhome. However, when Kimmel asked whether she believed in ghosts. Courteney Cox said as [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/courteney-cox-paranormal-encounter-haunted-home</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/courteney-cox-paranormal-encounter-haunted-home</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Will There Be a Ted Lasso Season 4? Is a 2025 Release Date Possible?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Could Ted Lasso Season 4 be in the works? The hit Apple TV Plus comedy series has already enjoyed three successful seasons. Starring Jason Sudeikis in the lead role, the show follows the journey of a bumbling American football coach who tries to turn around a struggling English soccer team. The series quickly became a [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/ted-lasso-season-4-release-date-plot</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/ted-lasso-season-4-release-date-plot</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sam Elliott considers Benedict Cumberbatch's The Power of the Dog "a piece of s**t" for the following reasons.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Power of the Dog, a hotly anticipated western movie that came out last year, received high praise from numerous critics but fell short of Sam Elliott&#8217;s expectations. The Ghost Rider actor has made a name for himself in the western cinema industry by appearing in a number of them, but in a recent interview [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/sam-elliott-considers-benedict-cumberbatchs</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/sam-elliott-considers-benedict-cumberbatchs</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Netflix Stranger Things Canceled: Why Is There No Season 6?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Many fans of Stranger Things have been wondering whether the show is canceled since the announcement that the fifth season will be the last. Given Netflix&#8217;s tendency to end shows early, it is understandable to question whether this is the reason why there won&#8217;t be a Stranger Things Season 6. Did Netflix cancel Stranger Things [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/stranger-things-canceled-why-theres-no-season-6</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/stranger-things-canceled-why-theres-no-season-6</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robert Pattinson recounts how Zoe Kravitz 'punched him' while preparing an action scene for The Batman]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Batman film, starring Robert Pattinson and Zoe Kravitz, received favorable reviews from critics upon its release. The film, directed by Matt Reeves, has been dubbed &#8220;the darkest Batman film.&#8221; The film&#8217;s promos have already promised that it will be gritty, and one scene that has piqued everyone&#8217;s interest is the action sequence between Robert [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/robert-pattinson-zoe-kravitz-punched-him-batman</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/robert-pattinson-zoe-kravitz-punched-him-batman</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amy Schumer on her decision to undergo liposuction: I never saw myself doing something like that]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Amy Schumer has spoken out about her decision to have liposuction surgery. Chelsea Handler, 40, opened out about her thought process on the March 3 episode of her podcast Dear Chelsea. &#8220;I underwent liposuction. &#8220;I never thought I&#8217;d do something like that,&#8221; Amy Schumer stated. &#8220;Like, when I heard liposuction, I was like, &#8216;That&#8217;s insane [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/amy-schumer-undergo-liposuction</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/amy-schumer-undergo-liposuction</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robert Pattinson is being eyed for a reboot of The Crow]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Batman interviews have revealed a lot about how Robert Pattinson picks his roles. Specifically, the actor has told his agent that he wants to play &#8220;freaks.&#8221; With his DC picture finally releasing to great box office success and his Twilight history presumably behind him, studios will be looking at what options they have that [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/robert-pattinson-eyed-for-the-crow</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/robert-pattinson-eyed-for-the-crow</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amber Heard reveals that she wishes to have a career like Angelina Jolie]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2022, Amber Heard has been on screen pretty much every day, but not just as an actor. The bitter defamation trial between her and Johnny Depp was shown live on TV, streamed online, and recapped every day. This put both of them in front of millions of people every day. Heard&#8217;s [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/amber-heard-wishes-career-like-angelina-jolie</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/amber-heard-wishes-career-like-angelina-jolie</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rocky, the iconic character was supposed to die in one of the early Rocky movies, Sylvester Stallone reveals]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[For better or worse, the successful Sylvester Stallone movie Rocky has turned into a successful franchise that continues to this day with the successful Creed series of films. But that franchise and Sylvester Stallone&#8217;s character almost died decades ago. According to Slash Film, the actor from Tulsa King, who is now executive producing a new [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/rocky-sylvester-stallone-death-plot</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/rocky-sylvester-stallone-death-plot</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The film that Sylvester Stallone describes as "one of the worst films in the entire solar system"]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Although Sylvester Stallone initially struggled to establish his career, he earned popularity after writing and portraying the titular character in 1976&#8217;s Rocky. Over the years, the actor penned five sequels, solidifying his place as one of America&#8217;s top actors. By the 1980s, Sylvester Stallone was also well-known for his portrayal of action hero John Rambo [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/sylvester-stallone-describes-worst-film</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/sylvester-stallone-describes-worst-film</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Salma Hayek of Magic Mike confesses she almost flashed co-star]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Magic Mike&#8217;s Last Dance is now in theatres! Although the film has received mixed reviews thus far, no one can deny the chemistry between co-stars Salma Hayek and Channing Tatum. And it turns out that the actors almost got too close, with Salma Hayek describing how a dance rehearsal nearly saw her expose it all [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/salma-hayek-magic-mike-flashed-co-star</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/salma-hayek-magic-mike-flashed-co-star</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dave Bautista won't be playing his favorite DC Universe villain but teases playing the baddest one, Lux Luthor]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[DC Studios fans can&#8217;t wait to find out what CEOs James Gunn and Peter Safran have planned for the DC Extended Universe. A post on Instagram gives fans something new to look forward to. It showed a side-by-side comparison of Dave Bautista and Lex Luthor, which suggested that Bautista might be a good fit for [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/dave-bautista-dc-universe-lex-luthor</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/dave-bautista-dc-universe-lex-luthor</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mark Wahlberg reportedly got paid $30 million for the Netflix movie, "Spenser Confidential"]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spenser Confidential might not have got good reviews from the critics but Mark Wahlberg sure did make a lot of money from it. A report says that the actor was paid a lot of money for his work on the 2020 Netflix action comedy directed by Peter Berg. &nbsp; Mark Wahlberg earned an eight-figure paycheck [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/mark-wahlberg-spenser-confidential-netflix</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/mark-wahlberg-spenser-confidential-netflix</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clint Eastwood starred in and directed this top-streaming "underrated" movie]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Clint Eastwood is almost always the best choice for creative people who want to try their hand at acting and directing. From American Sniper with Bradley Cooper to Invictus with Morgan Freeman and Matt Damon, the actor-turned-director has made quite a name for himself behind the camera. Right now, people on HBO Max can&#8217;t get [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/clint-eastwood-heartbbreak-ridge-hbo-max</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/clint-eastwood-heartbbreak-ridge-hbo-max</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lucky Hank Episode 7: “The Count of Monte Cristo” - Release Date, Time & Where to Watch the Bob Odenkirk Series]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[About Lucky Hank Lucky Hank is a new series created by Bob Odenkirk, based on the novel Straight Man, released in 1997. The show revolves around Professor Hank Devereaux, an English department chairman at an underfunded college who struggles to balance his personal and professional life. Hank is going through a midlife crisis, and the [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/lucky-hank-episode-7-preview</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/lucky-hank-episode-7-preview</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Family Guy Season 21 Episode 18 Recap & Review: “Vat Man & Rob ‘Em” - Peter's Night Watchman Adventures & Brian's Daring Dog Deception]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction Welcome to the recap and review of the latest episode of Family Guy, titled “Vat Man &amp; Rob ‘Em.” This episode takes us on an exciting journey with our favorite characters navigating through hilarious and unpredictable situations. In this episode, Peter takes on the night watchman job at his brewery after the previous watchman [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/family-guy-season-21-episode-18-vat-man-rob-em</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/family-guy-season-21-episode-18-vat-man-rob-em</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Simpsons Season 34 Episode 18: “Fan-Ily Feud” - Recap, Review & Homer's Battle with Pop Star Fandoms]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Fan-Ily Feud In this episode of The Simpsons, Homer takes Bart to watch a baseball match at Isotope Stadium. Still, things turn sour when an advertisement for pop singer Ashley Starling&#8217;s newest single plays on the jumbotron. Bart expresses his disdain for Ashley, calling her a &#8220;whiny pop singer for whiny girls that love to [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/the-simpsons-season-34-episode-18-fan-ily-feud</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/the-simpsons-season-34-episode-18-fan-ily-feud</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lucky Hank Episode 6: “The Arrival,”: Release Date, Time & Where to Watch the Bob Odenkirk Series]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Arrival In episode six of Lucky Hank, titled “The Arrival,” Hank waits for William to arrive outside Taylor Manor, where his mother lives. The big question in this episode of Lucky Hank is whether Hank will confront the ghosts of his past and seek closure so he can start caring again. Plot Summary Lily [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/lucky-hank-season-1-episode-6-the-arrival</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/lucky-hank-season-1-episode-6-the-arrival</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Barry Season 4 Episode 3 Recap: 'You're Charming' Plot Twists, Shootout, and New Characters]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction In episode 3 of the fourth season of &#8220;Barry,&#8221; titled &#8220;You&#8217;re Charming,&#8221; the operation that Cristobal masterminded with the Chinese and Guatemalans turns out to be successful. Meanwhile, Hank hires the help of El Toro, a new character introduced in this season, to assassinate Barry. The episode is filled with action and twists that [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/barry-season-4-episode-3-recap-youre-charming-plot-twists-shootout-and-new-characters</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/barry-season-4-episode-3-recap-youre-charming-plot-twists-shootout-and-new-characters</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Bruce Willis wasn't the studio's first pick for 'Die Hard']]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Today, Bruce Willis is most known for his portrayal as John McClane in the Die Hard franchise. The Die Hard franchise has sold out movie theatres for nearly three decades, beginning with 1988&#8217;s Die Hard and ending with 2013&#8217;s A Good Day to Die Hard. Following Die Hard, Willis established himself as a true action [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/why-bruce-willis-not-first-pick-for-die-hard</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/why-bruce-willis-not-first-pick-for-die-hard</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Angelina Jolie once spit in Colin Farrell's face in the film 'Alexander' out of rage]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Angelina Jolie previously collaborated with Colin Farrell in Oliver Stone&#8217;s Alexander. Jolie reacted passionately and unexpectedly to her co-star during a frightening scene while filming with Farrell. Angelina Jolie originally thought being cast in ‘Alexander’ was ‘ridiculous’ Jolie&#8217;s casting in Stone&#8217;s 2004 film raised a few eyebrows. As the title suggests, Alexander was Stone&#8217;s take [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/angelina-jolie-spit-colin-farrells-face-in-film</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/angelina-jolie-spit-colin-farrells-face-in-film</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chainsaw Man Chapter 128 Released! Read Online, Manga, Spoiler Summary, Raw Scans and More]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The highly anticipated Chainsaw Man Chapter 128 of the manga series has finally been released, and it&#8217;s time to delve into all the exciting details. This latest installment promises to be full of action, suspense, and unexpected twists, leaving readers on the edge of their seats. Chainsaw Man is among the best selling manga. Due [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/chainsaw-man-chapter-128-release-date-spoilers</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/chainsaw-man-chapter-128-release-date-spoilers</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gerard Butler was once rebuked for saying that while working with Angelina Jolie, he had to dumb down his acting]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Angelina Jolie has collaborated with a wide range of actors, including her Lara Croft co-star Gerard Butler. However, the Plane actor once made a passing remark about the actor that put him in hot water. Angelina Jolie thought Gerard Butler could be her equal in ‘Tomb Raider: The Cradle of Life’ Cradle of Life was [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/gerard-butler-angelina-jolie-dumbed-down-acting</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/gerard-butler-angelina-jolie-dumbed-down-acting</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blue Lock Chapter 218 Release Date, Spoiler, Reddit Leak Status, Read Online, Raw Scan And More]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Japanese manga Blue Lock has fans all over the world who are always crazy to know more. Since a new chapter of the manga will release in a couple of days, we have some updates for you. Here’s all you need to know about Blue Lock Chapter 218! Release date of Blue Lock Chapter [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/blue-lock-chapter-218-release-date-spoiler</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/blue-lock-chapter-218-release-date-spoiler</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fairy Tail 100 Years Quest Chapter 132 Release Date, Spoiler, Read Online, Raw Scan And Spoiler]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In Fairy Tail 100 Years Quest Chapter 132, we can expect more action, adventure, and surprises from our favorite mages. With the previous chapter leaving us on a cliffhanger, fans are eagerly waiting to find out what happens next. Release date of Fairy Tail 100 Years Quest Chapter 132 BREAKING: Hiro Mashima has confirmed yesterday [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/fairy-tail-100-years-quest-chapter-132-release-date-spoiler-read-online-raw-scan-and-spoiler</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/fairy-tail-100-years-quest-chapter-132-release-date-spoiler-read-online-raw-scan-and-spoiler</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Boruto Chapter 80 Spoilers Review: Eida's Reality Manipulation and Boruto's Willpower]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Boruto Chapter 80 spoilers reveal that Eida&#8217;s reality manipulation won&#8217;t crush the Hokage&#8217;s son, instead he views it as a challenge to overcome. Warning: The below text contains Boruto Chapter 80 spoilers: Naruto Next Generations, &#8220;What Dad Would Do!,&#8221; created by Masashi Kishimoto, Mikio Ikemoto, Mari Morimoto, and Snir Aharon. The chapter is now officially [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/boruto-chapter-80-spoilers-review</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/boruto-chapter-80-spoilers-review</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dragon Ball Super Chapter 93 Release Date, Spoilers, Read Online, Reddit Leaks, Raw Scans and More]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Dragon Ball Super Chapter 93 is just around the corner, and fans are eagerly anticipating the latest developments in the ongoing saga. With the manga series entering a new arc, excitement is at an all-time high as readers speculate about what&#8217;s to come. Release date of Dragon Ball Super Chapter 93 You can only have [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/dragon-ball-super-chapter-93-read-online-spoiler</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/dragon-ball-super-chapter-93-read-online-spoiler</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Watch American Idol Season 21 Online Hulu, Disney, YouTube, Netflix Detailed Streaming Guide]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[There are multiple ways to stream American Idol Season 21 online in 2023. The latest season has been entertaining viewers since the time it premiered on February 19, 2023. This article will reveal every possible way to watch the new season on multiple platforms. American Idol Season 21’s excitement is at a high time since [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/american-idol-season-21-watch-online-2023</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/american-idol-season-21-watch-online-2023</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jennifer Aniston admits to have been left "confused" after the end of her marriage to Brad Pitt]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[About sixteen years ago, everyone watched as Jennifer Aniston and Brad Pitt&#8217;s marriage fall apart. Pitt&#8217;s affair with Angelina Jolie on the set of the 2005 movie Mr. and Mrs. Smith put a quick end to what seemed like a perfect marriage. The former member of Friends has moved on and stopped thinking about that [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/jennifer-aniston-brad-pitt-marriage-confused</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/jennifer-aniston-brad-pitt-marriage-confused</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rain Dogs Season 2 Release Date, Renewal Status, Online Streaming Guide & Cast]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Fans might get to see Rain Dogs Season 2 as positive reviews pour in for the latest episodes of Season 1. The show, co-produced by BBC and HBO, has managed to win hearts due to its handling of some really complex themes. Let us know in detail about RainDogs Season 2 Release date, renewal status [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/rain-dogs-season-2-release-date-renewal</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/rain-dogs-season-2-release-date-renewal</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tokyo Revengers Season 2 English Dub Release Date, Reason For Delay & Everything Else You Need To Know]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Have you been searching for Tokyo Revengers Season 2 English dub release date? Well, fans of this popular anime series have been awaiting the release date for the dubbed version for a long. The dubbed episodes were delayed but finally, fans can get to watch them. Tokyo Revengers Season 2 released in January 2023. Fans [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/tokyo-revengers-season-2-english-dub-delay</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/tokyo-revengers-season-2-english-dub-delay</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Boruto Chapter 81 Release Date and Spoilers Review: Time-Skip is Almost Confirmed]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Boruto Chapter 81 could be the most important one in the series so far since it is very heavily speculated that this chapter will kick start the time skip and be a turning point in the manga. The Boruto fandom was thrilled by the release of chapter 80, which brought an end to the first [&hellip;]]]></description>
            <link>www.hiptoro.com/p/boruto-chapter-81-release-date-spoilers</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">www.hiptoro.com/p/boruto-chapter-81-release-date-spoilers</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>